https://www.ericross.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
SECTION 1 – WHAT DO WE DO WITH YOUR INFORMATION?
When you purchase something from our store, as part of the buying and selling process, we collect the personal information you give us such as your name, address and email address.
When you browse our store, we also automatically receive your computer’s internet protocol (IP) address in order to provide us with information that helps us learn about your browser and operating system.
Email marketing (if applicable): With your permission, we may send you emails about our store, new products and other updates.
SECTION 2 – CONSENT
How do you get my consent?
When you provide us with personal information to complete a transaction, verify your credit card, place an order, arrange for a delivery or return a purchase, we imply that you consent to our collecting it and using it for that specific reason only.
If we ask for your personal information for a secondary reason, like marketing, we will either ask you directly for your expressed consent, or provide you with an opportunity to say no.
How do I withdraw my consent?
If after you opt-in, you change your mind, you may withdraw your consent for us to contact you, for the continued collection, use or disclosure of your information, at anytime, by contacting us ateric@ericross.com or mailing us at:
Eric Ross Winery
14300 Arnold Drive
Glen Ellen , CA 95442
SECTION 3 – DISCLOSURE
We may disclose your personal information if we are required by law to do so or if you violate our Terms of Service.
SECTION 4 – ACTIVE CLUB SOLUTION
Our store is hosted on Active Club Solution Inc. They provide us with the online e-commerce platform that allows us to sell our products and services to you.
Your data is stored through Active Club Solution’s data storage, databases and the general Active Club Solution application. They store your data on a secure server behind a firewall.
Payment:
If you choose a direct payment gateway to complete your purchase, then Active Club Solution stores your credit card data. It is encrypted through the Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard (PCI-DSS). Your purchase transaction data is stored only as long as is necessary to complete your purchase transaction. After that is complete, your purchase transaction information is deleted.
All direct payment gateways adhere to the standards set by PCI-DSS as managed by the PCI Security Standards Council, which is a joint effort of brands like Visa, Mastercard, American Express and Discover.
PCI-DSS requirements help ensure the secure handling of credit card information by our store and its service providers.
For more insight, you may also want to read Active Club Solution Privacy Statement (https://www.secureclub.net/images/activeclubmgmt/Active%20Club%20Soutions%20Privacy%20Policy%20November%202016.pdf).
SECTION 5 – THIRD-PARTY SERVICES
In general, third-party providers used by us will only collect, use and disclose your information to the extent necessary to allow them to perform the services they provide to us.
However, certain third-party service providers, such as payment gateways and other payment transaction processors, have their own privacy policies in respect to the information we are required to provide to them for your purchase-related transactions.
For these providers, we recommend that you read their privacy policies so you can understand the manner in which your personal information will be handled by these providers.
In particular, remember that certain providers may be located in or have facilities that are located a different jurisdiction than either you or us. So if you elect to proceed with a transaction that involves the services of a third-party service provider, then your information may become subject to the laws of the jurisdiction(s) in which that service provider or its facilities are located.
As an example, if you are located in Canada and your transaction is processed by a payment gateway located in the United States, then your personal information used in completing that transaction may be subject to disclosure under United States legislation, including the Patriot Act.
Once you leave our store’s website or are redirected to a third-party website or application, you are no longer governed by this Privacy Policy or our website’s Terms of Service.
Links
When you click on links on our store, they may direct you away from our site. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites and encourage you to read their privacy statements.
SECTION 6 – SECURITY
To protect your personal information, we take reasonable precautions and follow industry best practices to make sure it is not inappropriately lost, misused, accessed, disclosed, altered or destroyed.
If you provide us with your credit card information, the information is encrypted using secure socket layer technology (SSL) and stored with a AES-256 encryption. Although no method of transmission over the Internet or electronic storage is 100% secure, we follow all PCI-DSS requirements and implement additional generally accepted industry standards.
SECTION 7 – COOKIES
On our website, we use a tool called “Google Analytics.” This tool collects the IP address of every visitor to our website, including yours, on the date you visit our website. The tool does not capture your name or any other identifying information.
The Google Analytics tool also plants a permanent cookie, a special text file, on the web browser of every visitor to our website to identify each visitor as a unique user the next time the visitor accesses our website.
Through the use of cookies, Google Analytics provides with information about how often users visit our website, what pages they visit, when they visit, what other sites they accessed prior to coming to our website and other related information.
We use the information we receive through Google Analytics to improve our website. We do not combine the information we receive from our use of Google Analytics with other personal information. Google’s ability to use and share information collected by Google Analytics about your visits to this website is restricted by the Google Analytics Terms of Use available at https://www.google.com/analytics/terms/us.html and the Google Privacy Policy available at http://www.google.com/policies/privacy.
You can prevent Google Analytics tool from recognizing you on return visits to this site by disabling cookies on your browser.
Other Third Parties.
We may also collect your personal information from other third parties, when we receive your personal information from our marketing partners, social media platforms or purchased or publicly available databases.
Information Use.
We use the personal information we collect from you and third parties to:
• Send you information about our products and services
• Fulfill orders for our products and services
• Administer customer accounts
• Invite you to attend marketing events or participate in promotional activities
• Personalize your experience with our products and services by tailoring offerings and services to your interests
• Provide technical support for our products and services
• Monitor the security of our technology environments
• Research and analyze how our product and services are used
• Improve our products and services, including our website
Usage and Analytics Data.
We also collect and analyze data about your use and configuration of our products and services and the operating environments in which our products and services are used. We collect and analyze this data in order to (a) provide and maintain our products and services, (b) anticipate and address future customer needs and (c) ensure that our products are not being misused.
SECTION 8 – AGE OF CONSENT
By using this site, you represent that you are at least the age of majority in your state or province of residence, or that you are the age of majority in your state or province of residence and you have given us your consent to allow any of your minor dependents to use this site.
SECTION 9 – CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY
We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time, so please review it frequently. Changes and clarifications will take effect immediately upon their posting on the website. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here that it has been updated, so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we use and/or disclose it.
If our store is acquired or merged with another company, your information may be transferred to the new owners so that we may continue to sell products to you.
QUESTIONS AND CONTACT INFORMATION
If you would like to: access, correct, amend or delete any personal information we have about you, register a complaint, or simply want more information contact our Privacy Compliance Officer at eric@ericross.com or by mail at
Eric Ross Winery
[Re: Privacy Compliance Officer]
"Taste The Vineyard"
That's what the wine should reflect.
Copyright © Eric Ross Winery – 2018
